<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AyurvedaApp</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="click1">Upload</string>
    <string name="click2">Save</string>
    <string name="text1">Please Click 4 pictures of the leaf</string>
    <string name="note1">Pictures with flash ON</string>
    <string name="note2">Pictures with flash OFF</string>
    <string name="text2">Picture of front face : </string>
    <string name="text3">Picture of back face : </string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="tulsi">Order\t\t\t\t: Lamiales\nFamily\t\t\t\t: Lamiaceae\nGenus\t\t\t\t: Ocimum\nSpecies\t\t: O. tenuiflorum\n\t\t\tTulasi (Sanskrit:-Surasa) has been used for thousands of years in Ayurveda for its diverse healing properties. It is mentioned in the Charaka Samhita,an ancient Ayurvedic text. Tulsi is considered to be an adaptogen, balancing different processes in the body, and helpful for adapting to stress. Marked by its strong aroma and astringent taste, it is regarded in Ayurveda as a kind of "elixir of life" and believed to promote longevity.</string>
    <string name="ammabhji">Family\t\t: Euphorbiaceae.\nHabitat\t: Occurs throughout the plains\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tof India, ascending the hills in\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tOrissa up to 200 m.\nEnglish\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Indian Acalypha.\nAyurvedic\t\t\t\t: Kuppi, Muktavarchaa,\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tHaritamanjari\nSiddha/Tamil\t: Kuppaimeni.\nFolk\t\t\t\t: Khokli, Kuppi, Aamaabhaaji.\nAction \t: Antibacterial (leaf used inscabies). Plant—emetic, expectorant(used in bronchitis, asthma,pneumonia). Tincture of fresh plant is used in homoeopathy for incipient phthisis with bloodyexpectorations, emaciation and arterial haemorrhage. The plant contains kaempferol; leaves and twigs contain acalyphamideand other amides, quinone, sterols,cyanogenic glycoside. The herb causes intestinal irritation.</string>
    <string name="lemon">Order: Poales\nFamily: Poaceae\nSubfamily: Panicoideae\nTribe:	Andropogoneae\nSubtribe: Andropogoninae\nGenus:	Cymbopogon\nAction: By inhalation, the essential oil of lemongrass is used as aromatherapy for muscle pain. In food and beverages, lemongrass is used as a flavoring. For example, lemongrass leaves are commonly used as “lemon” flavoring in herbal teas. In manufacturing, lemongrass is used as a fragrance in soaps and cosmetics.</string>
    <string name="neem">Order: Sapindales\nFamily: Meliaceae\nGenus: Azadirachta\nSpecies: A. indica\nAction: Neem products are believed by Siddha and Ayurvedic practitioners to be Anthelmintic, antifungal, antidiabetic, antibacterial, antiviral, contraceptive, and sedative.[12] It is considered a major component in siddha medicine and Ayurvedic and Unani medicine and is particularly prescribed for skin diseases.[</string>
    <string name="ashwa">Order:	Solanales\nFamily: Solanaceae\nGenus: Withania\nSpecies: W. somnifera\nAction: Ashwagandha is used for arthritis, anxiety, trouble sleeping (insomnia), tumors, tuberculosis, asthma, a skin condition marked by white patchiness (leukoderma), bronchitis, backache, fibromyalgia, menstrual problems, hiccups, and chronic liver disease.</string>
    <string name="aloev">Order:	Asparagales\nFamily: Asphodelaceae\nSubfamily: Asphodeloideae\nGenus: Aloe\nSpecies: A. vera\nAction: Aloe vera contains something called proteolytic enzymes which repairs dead skin cells on the scalp. It also acts as a great conditioner and leaves your hair all smooth and shiny. It promotes hair growth, prevents itching on the scalp, reduces dandruff and conditions your hair</string>
    <string name="datura">Order: Solanales\nFamily: Solanaceae\nGenus: Datura\nSpecies:	D. metel\nAction: Datura metel is a shrub–like perennial herb, commonly known as angel\'s trumpet, devil\'s trumpet, and metel.Datura metel grows in the wild in all the warmer parts of the world, and is cultivated worldwide for its chemical and ornamental properties. It was first described by Linnaeus in 1753, but no botanically correct illustrations or descriptions were made until after the New World was settled. It is not possible to be sure about its original home.Principal Constituents Scopolamine (Hyoscine) is the major active constituent of the plant.\nPharmacology: Scopolamine has analgesic and sedative actions and produce amnesia1. It also has anti–inflammatory property.The plant is an annual herb growing up to 3 ft. high. It is slightly furry, with dark violet shoots and oval to broad oval leaves that are often dark violet as well. The pleasantly–scented 6–8 in. flowers are immensely varied, and can be single or double. Colors range from white to cream, yellow, red, and violet. The seed capsule is covered with numerous conical humps and a few spines.[1] It is similar to D. inoxia, but D. metel has almost glabrous leaves and fruits that are knobby, not spiny. D. inoxia is pilose all over and has a spiny fruit.</string>
    <string name="niruri">Family: Phyllanthaceae\nGenus: Phyllanthus\nSpecies: P. niruri\nAction: The annual herb Phyllanthus niruri is best known by the common names Stonebreaker(Eng.), Chanca Piedra(Sp.) and Quebra Pedra(Port.), Seed-Under-Leaf(Eng.) but has many other common names in assorted languages, including dukong anak, dukong-dukong anak, amin buah, rami buah, turi hutan, bhuiaonla, Meniran (Indonesia).The herb is known as Nela Nelli in Kannada and \"Nela Usiri\" in Telugu. It is a widespread tropical plant commonly found in coastal areas. It is a relative of the spurges and grows 50 to 70 centimeters tall and bears ascending herbaceous branches. The bark is smooth and light green. It bears numerous pale green flowers which are often flushed with red. The fruits are tiny, smooth capsules containing seeds.\nMedicinal: Uses Some of the medicinal properties suggested by preclinical trials are anti-hepatotoxicity, anti-lithic, anti-hypertensive, anti-HIV and anti-hepatitis B. However, human trials do not show efficacy against hepatitis B virus.P. amarus is an important plant of Indian Ayurvedic system of medicine which is used for stomach problems,and for the genitourinary system, liver, kidney and spleen. The plant has long been used in Brazil and Peru as a supposed herbal remedy for kidney stones. Research among sufferers of kidney stones has shown that, while intake of Phyllanthus niruri didn\'t lead to a significant difference in either stone voiding or pain levels, it may reduce urinary calcium, a contributing factor to stone growth. One study conducted on rats showed that an aqueous solution of Phyllanthus niruri may inhibit kidney stone growth and formation in animals who already have stones.</string>
    <string name="nyctanthes">Family: Oleaceae; Nyctanthaceae.\nHabitat: Outer Himalaya, Assam,West Bengal; cultivated in many parts of India.\nEnglish: Tree of Sorrow, Night Jasmine, Coral Jasmine.\nAyurvedic : Paarijaata, Shephaali, Shephaalikaa, Mandaara.\nUnani: Harasingaar.\nSiddha: Pavazha mattigai.\nAction: Leaves—bitter tonic, cholagogue,febrifuge, anti-inflammatory, antispasmodic, hypotensive, respiratory stimulant. Used for fevers, rheumatism, obstinate sciatica. The leaves and seeds contain iridoid glycosides; other constituents reported from the leaves are mannitol, beta-amyrin, beta-sitosterol, hentriacontane, benzoic acid, astragalin, nicotiflorin, oleanolic acid, nyctanthic acid, friedelin and lupeol. The seeds containa polysaccharide glucomannan. All parts of the plant are used for allergic disorders. Alcoholic extract of the plant was found to inhibit passive cutaneous anaphylaxis (PCA) in experimental animals. The inhibition was comparable to standard drugs used for allergy and bronchial asthma. Ethanolic extract of the leaves, flowers and seeds demonstrated strong stimulation of antigen specific and non-specific immunity in mice. The 20% ethanolic extracts of the leaves, flowers, seeds and roots were found effective in treating caecal amoebiasis caused by Entamoeba histolytica in rats. But the extracts did not exhibit direct amoebicidal activity in vitro against trophozoites of the parasite. The iridoid glucosides showed antileishmanial activity both in vivo and in vitro.Dosage :- Leaf—10–12 ml juice.</string>
    <string name="psoralea">Order: Fabales\nFamily:	Fabaceae\nGenus: Psoralea\nSpecies:	P. corylifolia\nHabitat Rajasthan., eastern districts of Punjab and adjoining areas of Uttar Pradesh.Ayurvedic Somaraaji, Somavalli, Somavallik, Soma, Chaandri, Vaakuchi, Baakuchi, Avalguja. Unani Baabchi, Bakuchi. Siddha/Tamil Karpoogaarisi.\nAction Seed: used in leucoderma, vitiligo, leprosy, psoriasis and inflammatory diseases of the skin, both orally and externally.(The Ayurvedic Pharmacopoeia of India.) The seed and roots contain chalcones, flavones, isoflavones, furanocoumarins and coumesterol group of compounds. These include psoralen,isopsoralen, bavachinin. A mixture of psoralen and isopsoralen,present, is recommended for topical application in leucoderma.These furanocoumarins initiate transformation of DOPA to melanin under the influence of UV light. Seeds are powdered and administered orally with warm water (1 g/day) in cases of eczema. Psoralen was found to be cytotoxicin vitro. The combination therapy of psoralen and UV irradiation has been shown to inhibit the growth of tumours in vivo. Bavachinin-A, isolated from the fruits, exhibited marked anti-inflammatory, antipyretic and mild analgesic properties similar to those of oxyphenylbutazone and hydrocortisone. It demonstrated better antipyretic activity than paracetamol experimentally. Oral administration of the powdered seeds has generally resulted in side reactions (nausea, vomiting, purging); external application generally proved highly irritant to the skin. Dosage Seed—0.5–1 g powder; 2–3 g powder </string>
    <string name="rauwolfia">Order:	Gentianales\nFamily: Apocynaceae\nGenus: Rauvolfia\nSpecies: R. serpentina\nIt is one of the 50 fundamental herbs used in traditional Chinese medicine, where it has the name shégēn mù (Chinese: 蛇根木) or yìndù shémù (Chinese: 印度蛇木). Rauwolfia serpentina contains a number of bioactive chemicals, including yohimbine, reserpine, ajmaline, deserpidine, rescinnamine, serpentinine. Reserpine has a highly complex pattern of activity. Besides the amine concentration in brain, it is also reported to influence the concentration of glycogen, acetyl choline, g–amino butyric acid, nucleic acids and anti–diuretic hormone. The effects of reserpine include respiratory inhibition, stimulation of peristalsis, myosis, relaxation of nictating membranes, and influence on the temperature regulating centre. It increases the volume and free acidity of gastric secretion. Reserpine reduces glycaemia in some cases but the effect is short–lived. In some patients it has a stimulating effect on prothrombin activity. Reserpine also favors permeation of blood into areas rendered ischemic by burns1. It produces sedation and a lowering of blood pressure. If administered orally, in hypertension, the effects of reserpine are slow, seldom appearing before 3–6 days of administration and continuing for some time after withdrawal of the drug and have a cumulative effect. It is most valuable in young patients with mild labile hypertension associated with tachycardia. In long established hypertension, it is best used in conjunction with more potent hypertensive drugs such as hexamethonium or hydralazine. Combined with polythiazide, it is a useful hypotensive in mild to moderate thiazide, it is a useful hypotensive in mild to moderate conditions. The response to reserpine varies in patients and the dosage must be adjusted to individual requirements. In severe hypertension, it may be given by intravenous or intramuscular injection when the effect begins within a few hours. Parenteral therapy of reserpine is indicated in the treatment of hypertension only when oral administration is impracticable</string>
    <string name="siris">Family: Mimosaceae.\nHabitat: All over India, from the Heights up to 1000 min theHimalayas;also in the Andamans.\nEnglish :- Siris tree, East Indian walnut.\nAyurvedic :- Shirisha, Bhandi,Bhandila, Shitapushpa, Mridupushpa,Kapitana (bark—dusty black).\nUnani: Siras.\nSiddha/Tamil: Vaagei.Action: Antiseptic, antibacterial, antiallergic, antidermatosis, antidysenteric. Bark—used in bronchitis;bark and seeds in piles; root in hemicrania; flowers in cough, bronchitis, tropical pulmonary eosinophilia, and asthma. Pod— antiprotozoal.\nAction: Bark—a decoction is given in rheumatism and haemorrhage. The bark contains beta-sitosterol and yields 10–15% tannins. An oleanolic acid saponin, proceric acid saponin mixture from seeds and root saponin exhibit spermicidal activity. </string>
    <string name="solanum">Order: Solanales\nFamily: Solanaceae\nGenus:	Solanum\nSpecies: S. trilobatum \nCommon name Purple Fruited Pea Eggplant, Thai nightshade • Marathi mothiringnee, thoodalam • Tamil Tuduvalai, Nittidam, Sandunayattan, Surai • Malayalam tutavalam, putharichunda, putricunta, puttacunta, tudavalam • Telugu alarkapatramu, kondavuchinta, mullamusti • Kannada Kakamunji, Ambusondeballi • Oriya bryhoti • Sanskrit achuda, agnidamani, agnidamini, alarka.\nAction: Purple Fruited Pea Eggplant is a thorny creeper with bluish violet flower, more commonly available in Southern India has been used traditionally in Siddha system of medicines to treat various diseases. This species is globally distributed in Indo-Malesia. Within India, it has been recorded in Peninsular India along the highway and waste lands. It has purple flowers shaped like potato flowers. The leaves have 3 or 5 lobes.</string>
    <string name="trapa">Order:	Myrtales\nFamily: Lythraceae\nSubfamily: Trapoideae\nGenus:	Trapa\nHabitat: Throughout India.\nEnglish: Water Chestnut.\nAyurvedic: Shrngaataka, Shrngaata, Shrngamuula, Trikota, Jalaphala,Trikonaphala, Paaniyaphala, Jalkanda, Trikona, Trika.Unani Singhaaraa.\nSiddha: Singara\nAction: The Ayurvedic Pharmacopoeia of India recommends the use of dried kernels in bleeding disorders, threatened abortion, dysuria, polyuria and oedema. Flour of dried kernels is used in preparations for breaking fast in India. The flour is rich in proteins and minerals. The flour, prepared from dried kernels, of red and white varieties contain: phosphorus , sulphur; calcium ,magnesium sodium,; and potassium, iron and manganese,respectively. Dosage: Dried seed—2–3 g powder. </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello fragment</string>
    <string name="euca"> Kingdom:	Plantae\n
Clade:	Angiosperms\n
Clade:	Eudicots\n
Clade:	Rosids\n
Order:	Myrtales\n
Family:	Myrtaceae\n
Subfamily:	Myrtoideae\n
Tribe:	Eucalypteae\n
Genus:	Eucalyptus\n
Eucalyptus species have attracted attention from horticulturists, global development researchers, and environmentalists because of desirable traits such as being fast-growing sources of wood, producing oil that can be used for cleaning and as a natural insecticide, or an ability to be used to drain swamps and thereby reduce the risk of malaria. Eucalyptus oil finds many uses like in fuels, fragrances, insect repellance and antimicrobial activity. Eucalyptus trees show allelopathic effects; they release compounds which inhibit other plant species from growing nearby.
</string>>
    <string-array name="leaf">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Eucalyptus</item>
        <item>Datura</item>
        <item>Siris</item>
        <item />
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    */

</resources>
